This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
The Battle of Marineford ended with a Navy victory.
Unable to save Ace's life, the injured Luffy was taken to Amazon Lizzie,
where he fell into despair.
But this is a story from another time.
Ten years ago, in the East Blue,
the brothers ran wild with dreams of a world full of adventure,
as well as the pirate flags they would someday fly.
Tucked away in Mount Corvo with Dedan and her mountain bandits,
Ace and Luffy took a vow of brotherhood with their friend and co-conspirator, Sabo.
We'll always be brothers and nobody can take that away.
From now on, we're honest-to-goodness brothers.
Cheers to that!
Brothers!
Too bad I'm gonna become a pirate and recruit the best cook before you do.
Yeah, you wish! I'm gonna be a pirate before either of you don't!
You little bastards are still spouting that pirate crap!
You're both gonna be Marines someday, even if I gotta beat some dignity into you!
We will stand on our feet.
Now this is how you live!
Uh-huh, no kidding.
What an awesome hideout!
So that's where they are!
Luffy becoming an apprentice?
A man who fought against the king of the pirates!
Seasons came and went, giving way to winter.
Sabo! He's coming at you! Don't let him escape!
No problem! I got this!
Good! He's running straight for the bay!
I got this!
Okay, Luffy! You're up!
Hello, food!
You can't get away!
I got him! You see that?
Wow, nice one, Luffy!
Alright, that's two in one day!
We're gonna have a ton of Danpa soup tonight!
Uh-huh!
I did it!
I can undo! Yay!
Uh, hey, Luffy!
Uh, hey, Luffy?
Behind you! Look out!
Behind me!
Whoa!
Whoa, he's big!
Wow!
Whoa!
He's big!
I did it!
I can undo! Yay!
Uh, hey, Luffy?
Behind you! Look out!
Behind me?
Whoa, he's big!
He must have smelled our dinner and came running.
He just wants the dumpa, Luffy! Get away from there!
Oh, I've never hunted anything so big!
This one is special to me!
Don't go get your own food!
Luffy, cut it out! He's way too tough!
We can get another one!
No! I said this one is special!
Get away, Kat! I'm gonna fault you!
That looks bad!
You okay?
I'll show you!
Go, go!
Round two!
Now go, go!
No, you don't!
Hey!
Well, he's busy!
I know!
I'll get you next time!
Sorry!
I know that was your first big kill and all.
He'll get over it, which is something we couldn't say if he got eaten.
Yeah, but that tiger cheated!
He can't steal from me!
I gotta teach him a lesson!
Whoa!
If you want to die that bad, don't take us with you!
Come on!
That's not funny!
Okay!
Oh!
Uh?
Whoa!
No!
Uh...
Ugh...
Huh...
Uh...
Uh!
Hurry!
Pull!
He's slipping!
Okay!
Sorry.
Well, today sucked.
Let's go to bed and hope tomorrow is better.
You mean going to bed makes it better?
Oh, I'm hungry!
Whose fault is that?
Ow!
The bridge thing was stupid,
but I don't blame Luffy for being mad about losing his catch.
He did pretty good out there today.
Yeah, except for the part where he almost got eaten
by a giant tiger.
Oh, you would do the same thing.
Whatever.
Good night.
Having Big Brother sure is cool.
I hope they'll join my pirate crew someday.
Don't waste your time on these guys, Captain.
Yeah, we got this one.
I may be the Captain, but we're still brothers.
Awesome.
This had better be a really good joke.
I'd rather have something to eat, but let's hear it.
I'm happy, that's all.
I made up my mind.
You guys are joining my crew, okay?
Promise?
I'm not promising anything.
Shut up and go back to sleep.
I said we'd figure it out later, didn't I?
Aw, come on.
It'll be way more fun if we're together.
And you guys need my help, you know.
You do?
Uh, yeah, you're the one who needs help, buddy.
Also, stop bobbing like that.
It's weird.
You're not listening.
We've got to be a crew, we gotta.
Okay, I get it.
We make a good team.
Let's work together.
But I'm the captain.
No, it's my ship.
I see.
Well, that's too bad.
We're back to square one.
Are you sure you can't budge?
Yep.
What about you?
I want to be free.
I'm not going to serve as somebody's lackey.
Sorry.
Come on, it'll be fun.
Oh, wait, I know.
Let's go fight that big old tiger
and whoever beats it gets to be captain.
Screw captain.
We'll all be tiger food.
Even if we could beat that thing, which we can't,
the chances of you doing it are like zero.
Yeah, if I thought it by myself.
That's why we'll fight it as a team
and just see who lands the final hit.
Now that's a plan.
You guys are going down.
Yeah, right.
Everyone ready?
Uh-huh.
These were hard to catch.
This is a waste of fish.
You knew they were bait.
We got to think bigger if we want to fight a monster like that tiger.
Oh, it sounds like he's on his way.
Greedy jerk, I'm beating you and I'm keeping my fish.
Let's do it.
Oh, oops.
That's not a tiger.
So now what?
Do we fight him instead?
We didn't invite you, Bear.
Go away.
Shoo, go on.
Actually, this guy might be nearly as strong as the tiger.
Either way, if we can't beat him, we can't beat our kitty friend.
All right, then.
Let's see if Big Hairy and Ugly makes for a good warm-up.
Pull.
Keep yapping.
I'm going to beat him.
Hey, no fair!
Cheater!
Yeah!
Ah!
He's not going to stop chasing us, is he?
We're going to die!
God!
Whoa, who's that guy?
Better move, whoever he is.
His name's Nagari.
I've seen him around Great Terminal.
Hey!
What are you doing, old man?
You got a death wish?
Run!
Huh?
Leave these boys alone.
It's time to return to the forest.
I said turn around and leave us be.
Hmm.
He stopped it.
Hmm...
He stopped it!
Just like shakes! So cool!
What? You used to be a pirate, Nagari? And a captain?
Indeed.
Yeah, I knew that already. I mean, you did that cool thing. Only a pirate captain could be that awesome.
What cool thing?
You know what I'm talking about? You made the bear go away. And all you had to do was look at him. Just like shakes.
Oh, I see.
He never seemed tough enough to be a pirate. Not to me. He was just weird.
Of course, lots of people at Grey Terminal are weird. But this guy would grab junk all day and then hammer it together and make, well, I don't even know what.
The other guys or Blue Jam's crew would pick on him, but he'd just sit there and take it.
Never fought back or said a word. Seemed pretty pathetic if you ask me.
Shows what you know, dummy. All captains are like that.
Now you're just making stuff up. Since when are you the pirate expert, huh?
Captains? Don't get worked up over losers. Shanks told me.
It's always Shanks with you.
Hey, here. Eat.
Eat.
Huh?
Help! Help! Help! Help! Help!
Hey, you gave him more than me.
Let her look next time, shrimp.
Hey, don't hold back, Noggity. You did save our lives.
Thank you. But it was no trouble.
So, you're obviously no pushover. What are you doing in a dump like Grey Terminal?
Hmm?
Hmm.
It's hardly a charming story.
Well, if you don't want to talk about it, it's not like I can force you.
No, I don't mind.
I assume you know the famous pirate Gold Roger?
Uh-huh. Of course I know. He was the king!
My men, at the height of our strength, challenged Roger to a fight.
Really?
A fight that we lost.
Put in our place, we all split up.
Everything went downhill after that. One thing led to another.
And here I am.
Frankly, it makes me wonder if I was worth anything to begin with.
You fought the King of the Pirates. That means you're cool. Win or lose.
Well, I'm not so sure. We got beaten pretty badly.
And at any rate, we certainly didn't feel very cool. So...
Oh, really? So Gold Roger was as tough as they say? Or tougher even?
Yes. But one man alone can only be so strong.
It was his crew that made him truly unstoppable.
Or rather, it was their teamwork, their camaraderie that impressed me.
It was an honor to see them in action.
Oh!
Oh, man. I guess I still got a long way to go before I'm tough like that.
Is that so? Are you planning on being a pirate someday?
I sure am!
And a captain, like me.
Mm-hmm. And a king!
Oh, wait! You can help me! Do you have any good pirating tips?
Mm-hmm.
How do I get super strong?
I gotta beat Ace and Sabo so I can be captain.
Is that how it works?
Uh-huh. Sure is. So can you train me?
Well, all right.
Really?
That's great! I'll start my training tomorrow.
Where did Ace go?
Uh, yeah. About that.
What?!
Called Roger as Ace's dad and he never told me?!
Yeah, well, it's a big secret. So keep it that way.
And while you're at it, don't mention it to Ace either.
He'll kill the both of us.
I don't get it!
It's a mystery to me, too. But I do know he hates Roger.
Why? I mean, that's his dad.
Doesn't mean he has to like him. Does it?
I know you guys still have it worse, but even if I did have parents, I was still all alone.
Sorry. I guess you're right.
Family or not, I guess some people in this world just aren't meant to get along.
Yeah, but most people don't have the King of the Pirates as their dad.
I know you want to ask him about Roger, and to be honest, I'd love to know myself.
But just lay off, okay? Do you promise?
Uh-huh, no problem.
Oh, and you too, Nagari.
I won't say a word.
But to think that Roger had a son, and he was right here all this time.
All right, there he is.
Looks like he calmed down, but play it cool just in case, got it?
Yeah. And do not mention Roger.
I know, I know, I know.
Hey, Ace, there you are. Didn't know you came home already.
Hey, Ace, there you are. Didn't know Roger was your dad and you hate him.
He didn't last five seconds.
Remember when we were going to drown you, because I'm kind of regretting that we did it right now.
Luffy.
Yeah?
Who told you all that?
Sabo did!
So tell me, was Roger awesome or super awesome?
Stop it! Be cool! This is the exact opposite of what I told you to do! You're gonna get us killed!
Ow!
Don't you ever speak that name in front of me again, got it?
Don't be stingy, I bet you got cool stories to tell.
You could have let me explain before you clobbered me over the head.
That's enough!
There!
I wanna hear pirate secrets, please!
Yeah! We're brothers, we can't hide things from each other!
Shut up! You're both dead to me!
Roger, Roger, Roger! He's your father, father, father!
Stop! His anger's making him stronger!
This is your fault for running your mouth in the first place, Sabo!
Ow! He had to learn someday!
No kidding me!
Let me say it again. From now on, you bastards are dead to me.
Oh yeah? Took the words out of my mouth!
Ugh!
Don't let me down, I'll be counting on you.
Got it. I'll leave no stone unturned.
Well, you heard the man.
We'll get right on it, boss.
Hold on. When you find him, don't do anything yet.
What?
The longer we make him wait, the more gratitude we can wring out of him.
Money's fine, but I want a favor, too.
He can wait for his dear Sabo a bit longer.
I see.
Keep an eye on him, but until I give you the order, don't snatch him up.
We will have a visit this spring.
Dogra! Mangra!
What is Goa? A country?
Uh, that's the country we live in.
Mount Corvo, Windmill Village, and Great Terminal are all part of Goa.
Hmph. I knew that.
It must be the end of the world.
I wasn't even sure you could read, and now you're reading the paper.
Frankly, it's kinda creeping me out.
Anyway, they're making a big deal about this visit, but it's not like they're gonna haul their asses all the way to our mountain.
Not that I'd want to see those pompous bastards anyway.
Celestial Dragons, no thanks.
Ace and Sabo visit Nagari to see how Luffy is faring in his new apprenticeship.
As the three boys compete to decide who will be captain, Nagari reminds them that it takes more than strength to be a leader.
Facing off with a massive tiger, they must find their answer in battle.
On the next, One Piece! The battle against the big tiger!
Who is going to be captain? I'm gonna be king of the pirates!